And that's all I have to do for the great of being for my second canceled one day.
If you're good, I'm just going to leave one.
All we're going to have the population is preparing to take over this.
Twenty-four-one, that's twenty-one, one, five, of other schools.
How are we in team today?
In general.
At several teams here.
There's a number here.
Cooks harder.
There's a number there.
They're all sort of back to that.
Safety and change.
Always work this year.
We have five teams in this year.
We're going to take the night.
The girl's high school.
And we're going to take the night.
Thank you very much.
I'll be back for about a six-minute.
There's a very good thing.
There's an intense look this day.
And I'm going to tell you how to take part in the night.
I'm going to thank you guys.
There's a really serious barriers.
And also the management leadership from this year.
And it's hard.
Any time we get opportunity to get a stand-for.
But I don't know if you can bring our kids.
We're going to take that hot place.
Thank you very, very much.
We'll take this opportunity to showcase one of the young men and women.
And accomplish this year's first session.
So at this time, a lot of these are very powerful coach.
We've also been able to open a show as a guarder.
And we can talk a little bit about the season and the roughest of course.
Very many time for us.
Obviously, now we get a bit of heat with your family somewhere.
And I'm going to learn a little bit about the show.
Hold in.
First of all, the week.
The administration.
Support all the things we do.
Obviously, the father later.
The community.
The mind.
Allow us to use the facility.
Those are the reasons.
We need time and the highest level within the building.
body things going in the positive direction, and it gets grass through this year.
It's going to be very tough for us to look at five state candidates at something.
It's really unfair for all classifications, and it's a very slow subject in mind, so we can
meet against, and we're ready to do that, and those three phases, those middle school,
macro, and they've passed on to the middle school, high school rules all back and back,
and then high school rules all over the first time, and we hope to take them on that trend,
and we hope to take them on high school, and they don't want to talk about the fact that we
must, as a goal, and see that they don't meet in broad schools, so, only this year's guys
are literally, but a lot of the days are out in the middle of the year, I think, and she puts up
a lot of the things that I do, which I personally want to do as well, and my body is like
Jay White, state champion of 108, and three times, go to Mr. Merrick, Jay's
hand up.
Jay Co. Hurrell won the 1,21-year-olds, state champion.
He won the state championship without 1, and goes to state champion in the
Marshall position.
A lot of teams, and a lot of teams have contributed.
And we had some second stand in the third fourth place.
It's placely high, and, what's actually interesting is the, we had several
freshman places in the walks which is 500, 14 year-old growth in the beginning.
So the views are looking bright, but, although they don't want to be home, those are
the hell.
They are all in the back, supported, and they are out.
Like I said, it's not that it's definitely not one person allowing us to have this community of all of them, it's an administration, support and facilities that provide them with, and these kids out here can't say nothing when they they bought them.
So thank you guys for the information.
Thank you.
A lot of people in front of us, national public safety, public education.
We have G.I. Barron.
She's right.
Well, thank you, Mary.
I appreciate the city council do this for our dispatchers.
The dispatcher is probably not able to be here tonight, but we have the adjourned.
One of our dispatchers in the room today, we want to say thank you to them for their dispatchers.
They may work in the individual for all public safety.
And I'm not going to have both to thank you not for the way you do for us.
Honestly, probably it was pretty cool.
Staff in public safety.
They take the initial phone call there.
We're so reason when you call 911.
And I call my voice and the administration.
And sure, you're someone's kind of sending a line for help.
And they help people generally in their course.
And we just can't thank them enough.
Thank you.
I want them in the air.
It is a birthday to Parker.
I'm sure she is here.
Do you have anyone there?
She's here.
So number five, set the agenda.
Chapter six, and we are going to move on.
Six, and we're attending.
Second.
Really?
Part.
Number 11.
Performer.
Transportation.
Proper.
Thank you.
Mayor.
And members of the State Council.
I was a little disappointed.
I thought they were here for this presentation.
I can't.
You know.
Excited.
My things I can't talk about in the process with the TTAs, or in the health facility,
you can take other.
This 100 page one.
Strasse, a whole color angle.
To make a situation.
It's now to the other.
Privileities.
They're not very easy to read or interpret.
But I get those.
The audit.
The audit that they need comes out.
and says these are the right numbers,
but it doesn't say anything at all about the number of me.
And so what we've done is we created another report
called the performer, the C.A.B. on the screen,
and the C.A. goes on like on our copy.
And very simply, what the performer is,
is if someone were to come to you and say,
okay, from us, the names of all C.A.B.
point, power of the name, on scale of 1.K.
Everybody can understand the answer.
If I say a 10, everybody understand the rest of the number
of C.A.B. on scale of 1.K.B.
and say, if I say 100, everybody understand the number
And so what we've done is we've taken this copyrighted
and that policy and we created basically
in just what the whole of the governments
are not really realizing that it would take off and go
to the global.
And now this is talking in college and university textbooks
as the lay and analyze the useful governments
in the names of C.A.B.A.B.
So what we've done is we've taken your auditing
legal statements and we've got to produce
basically a really down into a health and success
and sustain a building's cohort.
Honestly, it was zero to 10.
With 10 being excellent, an angel of health and success
and a zero being poor for the community and health and success.
And so the first two-degree papers kind of just described
is what I'm just told you.
But I will think it takes five
when you can kind of see how this will work
these out at the end of the time.
It's going to take you on the 20 by 20.
But your overall source you can see
are on this slide.
And then every slide we follow this is
a great shape that we look at
and we feel it's very important to this business.
And then we quantify this market and then
store it and then we average all those stores.
together. The way we've this is pretty simple, some people like visuals, so on the left side
is a bar or a graph chart or sometimes a pie chart to kind of show you a 10-year history
of what's happened, some people like narratives, so on the right is a very simple explanation
and narrative of words, and then other people just like that most, but out there that has a great
yellow and green thing on it, where you can catch the city and perspective where you score, and so
as you can see, this year we scored an over-sword at 8.1. That's better than the score we
had last year, which is a 7.7. Now, if you've got a little bit of perspective, we've performed
this for probably about a hundred different governments across the US and 11 international
governments that follow the US accounting, the US Department of Interior uses this model to determine how much
funding they have Americans in the Netherlands, the war, and the Virgin Islands and things
of that age. We had only had two governments in the 20-year history that performed in a ever-sword
in the Netherlands, and they only scored a 9.1.1.1 each and are both top and bottom. So any time you
can score into the 8's, it's a major accomplishment. So when we take that 8, we can break it down to
the 3 in the visual scores, because I talked about both health and success and sustainability all
in one's score, that's the 8.1. But I can't speculate that it was basically telling one of the
scores for each of those food components, and as you can see on the side, and then in
every period, for 2020 on our financial position score, that's our health picture, we score a 5.1.
Now, zero is 4, 10 is excellent, and a 5 is considered by the side of the side, and we're so
from another standpoint, we're roughly about a 6, our schedule. So the above side of the side
side, we're not crazy about 7 seconds. Our performance, which is the 12 months that ended
June 3 of the 20, is where we really had shown that we scored a perfect 10, which is actually
very difficult, because we had a really significant 12 months performance, so initially, even with
the effectiveness in early March, we actually saw increases in sales and new tax for 4 months,
March, April, May, June, as opposed to the deepest because of the pandemic. And so when we
score successfully on performance, it usually makes us a little bit better off, so that's why our
position score went from a 5 to a 5, 9. We actually had better performance in 2020 than we had in
19, but we had a really good performance in 19, also the score of the 9, this year we had 10, and then
as far as our capability was sustainability, those four don't change.
usually very much to usually relate to whether or not we're in control of our radio
streams or whether we're relying too much on taxes or whether we actually have the
ability to manipulate our services to generate or service revenue we need to
and basically also look at on tax burden on our systems and our debt for our
citizens and we saw roughly if you can see about an 8.1 I'm sorry about a 7.9
and we usually don't see that sustainability or capabilities for moving very much on
the radio basis so really from a position belt and a sustainability
or it does about as high as you can realistically get for a city of the size and be able
to sustain that over a period of time so that's really no loss light and I just
kind of want to get a kind of seat in your district and where the school was been
17 was a very weird anomaly as you notice all of the year you see the relatively
shade in the 7th or 8th except for 17 17 we had some trippy transaction before we had this
you say in that if you were called or we actually issued the debt in our own name
but yet the asset that we acquired the money to the university so we did report that
they gave it a report the asset and that makes their books look really good and they
are not so good for that year so now we can kind of recover from that process you can see
kind of stair set are really back up into the 8th which again is pretty good so I'm going to do
take a couple of slides and not board everybody's crazily just kind of take a couple of points
I'll leave you to slide a date where I talk a little bit about the general funds, unassigned
fund balance and that's just fancy words for how much carryover does the general fund have at the
end of the year to carryover in the next year what's unobligated, unassigned and committed and I
measure the things for a total ribbon string for that year and so as you can notice based on the
bar of the graph on the left we've been eating a letter at our unassigned fund balance for a number
of years and it actually made it a way down to about 5% of our annual revenues which didn't give us a very
good tool to be satisfactory we need to be at about 10% and so as you can see this last year it's gotten back
up to 9 but the general fund is not overloaded with hatch in other words it's just now kind of building
it's reserved back and we're at a minimum it should be I actually do a much more comfortable
about 15 and 20% cushion because I've seen one I saw a E-10% of their annual revenue string in one
transaction before and you got to have that ability to do that so so the general fund on time
to kind of recover and hold dead in the max.
Kind of what I wanted to show you of that.
And again, there's some coffee table reading on some other pages.
On page 10, I usually ask about the pension system.
Of course, our fire and police are covered by the state police pension system.
Therefore, we're not having to fund it,
doesn't have this making a contribution to the state.
And then the state system funds it.
We also have our own non-deformed inflation plan.
We're through the Oklahoma Municipal Retirement Fund.
We have to fund that plan at a hundred percent level at some point in time.
And as you can kind of see, we've struggled in the past 10 years.
In fact, I think it was 2013 when we actually shop
managing our own pension system, actually turned over to the Oklahoma Municipal Retirement Fund.
And since that point of time, you can kind of see how the percentage of funded plan and why
has actually gone that.
So we're about 77 percent funded now.
There was a county change in about 2016, 2015,
where they changed the way they happened to count to this,
which actually kind of hurt us a little bit.
But now that's been played for about five years,
you can say that the pension system and 80% funding pretty much indefinitely
as long as the size of the government doesn't contract significantly.
So as long as we have about the same number of employees now or more than that,
as long as we contribute what our actual real contribution is required to be.
And as long as the municipal retirement fund is that money in return
to about 7-5 percent, this plant funds itself.
So I'm not very concerned even though it's poor very well in the pension system.
You're scoring better than it was.
Several years ago it was under your own control.
I would imagine that some time I would extend the 15-20 years
that will continue to fund itself to where you'll be up to 100% level,
barring the other 14 transactions of the current.
One other thing I'll show you, that's kind of interesting is on page 15,
where I literally showed you the last seven or eight years
of all of the receipts that go into that store.
So you can kind of see that since we were talking about the financial position
or the health store, it's a very far right column, the fiscal 20,
and then you can see the bottom box on the far right column.
This is the 5.9 that I talked about on the first slide.
And you can see the stores of the prior or six or seven or eight years there.
And the store is one of those reasons.
So it allows you to track yourself a little bit of this yourself.
As far as the first component of that school.
All right, 10.
I'm flipping too.
to slide 17. I'll pick this slide to talk about on the next set of
ratios, because this one looks so weird. This is basically the change in
your network, so we call that position. So if you spin more money than
you bring in, your network goes down, and if you bring in more money than you
spin, then the network goes up. Normally, this kind of stair sets its way up a little
of the time, of course we have a really weird view in 17 with that
safety and that issue. Of course that year looks terrible, and then of course
it's worth finding years both before and after. This year we had a good
change in that position of 14. In other words, we basically increased our
network by nearly 15% for where we started the year at July 11, 19. So again, five
six of those benchmarks for creating your position. I'm sorry, your
performance for it. And the only other one I mentioned was on slide 21, which is
your cell tax. Your cell tax grows in the pandemic year 5.6% which is the
opposite of what I've already did to do, so I'm just showing it how much I've done. I
guess. I had actually predicted our system tax would plummet because of COVID and
obviously included networks. What happened in most communities is they're going to
say home and they still have to spend money and they spend it locally and therefore
your cell tax and your taxes grow up. Only good really large cities seem to have a little
bit of a drop, but I think that's because people would go into the larger cities, and
they just say, and they still spend money. And so we had a good year and I understand that
the eight months so far this year are even better. So I'm asking this whole
little pretty well next year also as far as cell tax grow. So the next slide on slide 22,
I'm showing you the track record of our performance ratio. And again, this will 20 on the
far right. Audit tour on far right column is the 10. Last year was 9 and then you had to
go back to say where you just kind of see what the performance was. The last set of ratios
are the capabilities of the local sustainability ratios. Again, this talks about how much of
our revenue that we're under direct control over whether or not our creators or happy with
our ability to pay the back when they load up some money, like through bonds or other debts. And
then of course we have a lot of capabilities because we don't have any general obligation bond
that are saying the entire 10% on that assessed by a position could actually be issued
in the form of a zero on that.
that we require our own people to get behind it.
And when the people vote for a geolondent,
they also vote for a property tax lending
to then pay off that debt.
Other than that, we don't get any problem tax.
We, as the city, only the counties and the schools
were seeing the problem taxes.
However, if you ever had a voter approved general
on the nation bondet that treats or something else,
we would then be allowed to have a let me just
and have to pay the debt, sort of.
So basically, that gives you a lot of capability
going forward in the future.
And that's why you pay the bill and see what those are
so far.
So again, on the last page of that set of ratios,
on slide three, you can kind of see the capability ratios
and the last seven or eight years of those to work.
But usually pay the bill, it doesn't change very much
from year to year or even we have to have a good decade
to significantly change my very much.
And as you can see, we put a round of savings
for as far as capability or sustainability.
So what I'm going to leave you with is I think
you had a great year as far as the national health and success
and sustainability this concern.
That is not about that, is probably going to go down here.
So I don't know if you can go up the tire,
it's realistic.
But the reason we're doing this is going to cause you
to be, you know, to be performing very well.
This is a 10, that's probably going to raise your health a little bit.
But you can only perform a 10 and so many years
and so I just want to caution you that.
Let's not get too overly excited.
But I think the good news is far as the national health and success.
So any questions about this report or any of the slide
or anything else that you'd like to talk about?
All right, let me just do a little bit of a part of the data.
Or a part of the simple.
So that I can work on the one way that I appreciate time.
And as always, if you get a chance to read more of this
and have a question, let's take a lesson up.
We'll come back up in the future.
Thank you.
12.
I authorized signature to sign it in the city of mind.
I helped my change on the availability of my membership,
my language, and change in the local development.
Good evening.
This time, this afternoon, you to authorize the city manager
to sign in the amendment to our health and document.
So we're asking for two changes.
And update to our eligibility for plan membership language.
Please, and fire, or in the state, the pension system,
and they have eligibility to retire after 20 years of service.
Not immediately employees are.
in the PMR and this is a little bit different.
So we thought as necessary to add this at a crisp language,
which makes it very clear that when a union police
or fire employee or tires after 20 years of service,
despite the radiation, this could be 51, 52 years old,
that they are eligible to purchase our retirement insurance.
So, pretty good to this language.
Like the issue change, that is not clear,
and we wanted that to be clear,
that those employees are in a different pensions.
So, the subject change, we're kind of excited about
one of this or a couple of years,
but it's changing our current documents,
so that a mental health benefits are paid at 80-20,
the same as physical health benefits at 80-20.
Previous to this, there were little bits on how many visits
you could have for mental health benefits,
and it did not pay at the same rate.
So, this isn't a rich benefit for employees,
so we think it's important to give them an option
and to stress that mental health is just as important as physical health.
Questions?
And just to let you know, any time we add a minute,
both of the city managers, the planned administrator,
try to find a document.
So any time we do a minute,
we have to set it aside,
and we go further before you,
and we find to have council approval,
which is why it's important to me.
That's a team.
We were in my vision of the people in whether policy,
the corporate is part of the city,
my number of virtual policy,
I have about two, three.
So, on this slide,
I think the government has an input to it,
but just to give you a brief history of why this is coming up now.
It's something we disaster quite a few years.
These situations, like in high-risk,
something with the sense,
when they have had an open,
but then they do,
we always have, you know,
who's a emergency person now,
who's not a emergency person now,
who can tell the work.
So, what we did is we basically reach out
to a lot of other municipalities
and say, hey,
we've got an echo in another policy.
Let us see what you do.
The main cities that we see
was from art and more star and water
in the sky and the unicorn.
Those are the four of which are pieces of theirs
and kind of pieces ours together.
By this point,
for this time before you,
it is,
and you don't have to see your answer that for review.
and we can discuss it and have seen their staff meeting.
So there's been an input on all of this.
The city manager, or he stands at me,
is the online person that can declare an implement whether or not.
Policy design is categories in the voice,
so we'll have emergency, non-ency, and telework.
And that would define our adoptive search.
So when you're hired, you'll understand what category you're in.
Policy is going to stay out of voice,
or if you compensate during this type of event.
So if you already have a vacation,
or if they stand up, we'll still take your vacation or sit there.
If you're an emergency employee, and you're not able to tell work,
you'll pay admin pay during your telework,
you'll be paying your regular pay.
Policy already stays that all of our employees
are subject to emergency call back in the necessary.
So then what the policy says is something that for a worker,
we have a problem with you today, but then the NHR come back,
then we would do an emergency call back.
That is already covered in emergency policy.
Part of time employees.
So this type of school time employees,
it also covers part-time employees,
and what they would be paying, if they're a non-ency employee,
is only hours to pay, will designated to work on that specific day.
It was already their day out, and that's where they off.
They would not be paying that pay.
And also, this policy does not pertain to employees
who are currently having their collective bargaining agreements.
So any of our union employees are not qualified as policy,
because that's something that will happen to appreciate them,
if we want to include that.
Would you have any?
Sorry, we listen to the question.
Here's a minute.
I did a question.
On the back of the mouth, those are the eyes out where I'm going to put in
a residential order or emergency employee.
We've got got those folks that can stay home with our home and how that works.
We're about to, the home to the hacker report.
Is there any kind of hazard?
If I take those folks for half a year, half a drop in the street,
to be in that dangerous situation.
So there is, and we have a lot of discussion about that.
So I explained to the, I was used to cities in the energy.
It's my umbrella with people companies under it.
And every single position in the city has a different essential job functions.
So in this case, I'm going to emergency person now.
I'm going to know, that's what I can consider.
If I'm not, they're also going to understand that.
All the cities that we talk to, none of them, pay hazard pay,
actually at high majority of the ones that we get visible,
make employees.
their own conversation to cover it. I think what we decided as of the team is that the
exception is that we shouldn't sell it down. Then we felt like we needed to pay admin pay
to those non-religency employees. But currently now, we discussed it as a group and didn't feel
like that or something we needed to do.
So I think that's a great way to remind them that we should make it very, very, very significant
situation that hasn't been evaluated with that. And there's a way to take care of our employees
as a collective support. And we just, we have paid assets out, but the city was a little bit
dead, paid, being a little bit of a deal, something to work with. But you really impressive
to watch the social spawn of the very, very interesting ones. The folks that came together
at the setup that actually didn't have the gun. And putting themselves out there every day
working in one of the black lines and about the safety bugs. In folks that came in the office,
they were working at the computer and I knew that. You know, we also thought it was very impressive to see
what the city was able to do. Thanks to Mr. David there and our team. What they had put out
and we were able to tackle the way that the hotel work was really what put us in a position
to be able to respond to the honesty. And we were able to make sure that we had systems out of the table.
Even the parameters they were managing for the loss of power and care for building and ensuring that
the activity still there. Well, people had access to the technical resources and the team put together
and did pretty good enough because of shitting the press of the team. This document is really a combination of what we felt
we could be put in place of that even forward, which would be even better compared to the next time
we could be able to do that in the city of what their roles and the chance of building,
but I am going to add that this team will continue to respond to the community,
whether or not to the legislation. Great document to be able to do it.
And I actually made the decision to do that to the future in the past.
I don't anticipate this big news where I'll do it.
We'll be able to do it on the journey of patients, but it's not that much of an obstacle or something.
So I will ask if you have to be able to read it, sir.
I added something for those folks, because the only thing I'm going to do is this is what's actually written in the name of that site.
And we're asking for these to be able to do this.
And we're going to put this all in.
You can say if they were to ask another to go out and do anything like I would ask them to maybe consider where we go for that's just being on what they're about to take the period.
Are you afraid to, but at least I don't know what I'm going to say, but at least I don't know what I'm going to say, but I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'll go up to Dr. Overs and Dr. Overs and Dr. Overs and Dr. Overs are up to the opportunity for water on the water or the water.
Our magic groups are out of the last one, then you have a problem.
Thanks to that, you know. The special of those applications.
It's one of the rare things that I'd like to use this, I hope.
If you will be, I say, GMP wants to hear about within most, I have the privilege of sitting
in Asia, I think.
There's a lot of work that manages to listen, a lot of thought, you know, whatever directed
against the system of movement.
Yeah, I mean I can't forget this little thing to do in a certain way.
In fact, we're looking to the back across the entire city of the whole of the city
I think considerations, but any other considerations, in fact, in fact, in the future
when you put that in mind as well on the board, certainly if that's a little countable.
Any other questions to your vote?
I want to look.
Thank you.
Thanks for the promotion.
You're very, very fortunate.
So, if you've made much of my previous step, look at that one thing, what's the best of something else?
Can we take a look around here?
You can always take a look.
Take a look.
One of the most important things we'll take a look at.
Take that part.
That's the one.
No, we'll take that.
Five.
Four.
Fifteen.
It says for a direct regulation for my immigration provision,
I'll take a look.
All right.
Just working through a non-decoration of those items, this is the fact that that's sort of less
off-rides it out to be offered to vote.
That's it.
Just a few more.
I'm going to talk about it because part of it, they always, they never want to get out of the letter after you start testing.
So, like, or options, over by the time the virus is thrown around.
And if you have any questions about what on the surface of the list,
Dr. Police has been, but I can tell you general rule is that,
we have been put in the surface, but we know that we're just going to throw away
a hat no real value, but they didn't have a bid number or a serial number
and we are disappointed in the surface.
So, we have some item that are after asking the surface to the surface.
We have some items that we're asking the surface to be destroyed.
These are mostly item three items that could possibly be able to get every item.
If it possibly has some personal information, we don't want it to get out of it.
Social security members are sent around.
So, some of them are going to be closed for surplus that we can destroy them.
And then there's your item that we want to put in the online option,
which is being noticed at that moment.
This is the third option that I will have to tell you,
and I'm really impressed with some of all over the country to get things,
but I have no idea if anybody wants it.
So, are there any questions?
You didn't think of that option?
It's going to be either a late April or early May.
I have a few more handy items.
I think the airport might have a couple of things.
There's a couple of solid waste vehicles that I might add.
So, if that casual come back, that's for that surplus,
and you will probably be on the option.
It's usually a handy option.
And it's really fun.
If you pay for these things, it's really interesting.
Think that you try to add a bit, or if you buy something over that
from the last five minutes, it's perfect.
Oh, I'm asking if you sell the rocket, do that, or I'm not there anymore.
Oh, I don't know.
Last year, we sold it.
I was going to add it, or I thought they were selling the rocket.
Well, I just don't know if I can sell it.
What is that?
It's a particular?
That, it means.
It means.
I'm gonna accept.
I'll second it.
Or could our first release cycle?
No.
Thank you, Christian.
You are welcome.
I know that in the last options.
That was, when we did not have a knowledge, we would read it.
It cost us nothing.
What is it?
For 100% in 2015, it is under a record division, from my, or a record version,
The advisory work is a group before the new development of the splash pad, outboard by a major party, this number.
Meaning, so we had really local tribes come to us.
They were, they come together and they've been awarded a grant for a size amount of money to add a nature park slash.
I'm flashing you into one of our parks.
You potentially decided to put it somewhere and then to be splash pad complex.
You send them a couple of locations.
You have an 100% agree on where you're going to put it.
And they were still working on a concept of what we're looking for tonight.
You went to the part school.
You got a third approval.
Until you're nine.
What we're wanting to do is assist your approval.
Continue before.
And you can give your blessing on this.
And so we're going to be fine to do that.
You can play a concept and a location.
We'll come back to you for your approval.
Which was a judge of the research.
I think one of the odd words of the letter show and the show.
The reason is not the ocean.
Was it a research audience?
Yes.
The show.
The odd words show me.
Yeah.
I'm just in the second.
I guess we're going to have a matter of a great, great deal.
May the year of the year be the third one.
I'm going to let you do it.
I should have brought that.
I think that's what we're going to do.
No, you're going to let that go.
I'm going to mention that we're going to get a little bit of this.
It is an awesome opportunity.
There's a tiny time and there's an asset organization.
Don't you use that.
We're going to give you a free, an attitude part.
No, great.
So we're excited.
It's supposed to be.
to be all natural, so wrong but it's really something I think adds to our community.
I'll say I have a big deal to you.
We have a partner.
All right.
Thank you.
We have a couple.
So last time we came to try to give, we were waiting still for the approval from the
state to allow us to put them in the water.
And we had received that approval.
From that, however, there was one situation to this would be the last time that they
would allow us to replace the water.
Normal liners used to allow us to be more than 10 to 15 years.
So we are now on a clock for looking at a recyclable.
But for now, we can have that approval.
So that was definitely a set and sound we needed to continue with for the airship pool.
That's pretty much that kind of thing.
It's quite a little heavy.
We've been accepting a sector of debt, a saffron, a nation of war, a big sea court, a massive
or a larger amount of business, a corporation, a pool on it, or a place, or a municipal.
So a lot of people are waiting for a state to come.
We went ahead and sent out a good package for replacing the pool liners.
So when we did get the rules to come into it, we'd be ready.
We received two days back, forth and premises came in at the lower price of 180,000, 300.
This is the company that put in the line at the first time, so they are another with our pool.
They filled once we do our part, we still have to do concrete work.
But once we get our out of the way, they give you their part about finance.
There still is some of the line, we're still left in the pool.
It is a lot of our money, but the lab, we're going to work on it, but the weather is now with grass growing in our sports.
We're at the last time to put on and less money.
They're wanting 75 cent per short, to move along.
As of now, we're looking at even more land, we're looking at about $6,500.
And they're good.
So we are still pulling the line out of this camp.
but there's still that possibility that there will be an act of charge for the line that I'm going to get here.
Justin, how come it goes from, I mean, up in the bids were so different.
I think it's, that one is double.
Yeah, I think what you have is you have someone who is, did not come out and look at it
and not when you get burned with a little bit and you have someone who has a scarcer,
you know, exactly what they're looking at.
Now, you can tell when it comes to a phone and a line or half,
rents it to charge in five cents, that's where it put,
the only time when you charge five dollars just where it put.
So I think it's just knowledge of what it's saying.
So, if I had to check it, we had to be in one of the exotic side of the whole line.
That's like right.
That, we do what we have not seen that yet.
We had a whole group of fun that said in a hundred and ninety thousand,
six hundred and twenty three dollars.
And that has accumulated over the years, plus of interest money from the plot.
The thing about it, we have here a group of allocated at a hundred and ninety four thousand,
but we haven't seen that yet.
We haven't got to close that all in the parts of the plot.
There's still some projects outstanding.
That might need that project for both simply has been approved and obligated.
We've actually, we just haven't received the funds for that.
If it closed, that would be out of my hand.
So, you said the line is in a thousand, four.
One, two, five.
One, two, three.
A sixty right.
Two, five.
Six.
Three.
Ten.
Four, eight.
Two, five.
Five.
I've got five.
Four.
There's five.
Two.
Four.
The one with six.
That's five.
Two.
It's seven.
Ten.
Two.
So we do have the money right now,
on the 19th of the year,
on the 19th, 20th of the year.
To go ahead and do the right of the repairs and all the people.
We get a switch over on our chemical last year.
And we have enough, you don't believe,
we need a courtesy or a poor man.
So that, that's the reason
about $8,000 there.
So, and, just the time,
we're on the Holy of the laundry last last year.
Right.
So, we essentially would take,
you know, a start-up running
and make the repairs now.
And so,
we'll get back to that.
So, we get things in my life.
We'll get back to that.
We'll start at that.
Well, I think the City Council,
I don't know if we're in here,
but then do it.
So, I'm going to ask the people.
the rest of the stuff we have to do and how they get them for about a little bit of the end.
So, well, they're on the five weeks. Do you encourage them that now? Or does that remind me of you?
Uh, it just really depends on how much slime it's like when I get here.
We're still in the work of the diligence. I love that, and I have any line a lot in the game here.
I just somehow.
Um, if the crew would deny, uh, we were going to have a couple of weeks.
Or then they even did their time to take the work and adjust it together.
And, uh, I mean, we still need to our company work for the editor.
Uh, uh, five weeks.
We talked five weeks and then, you also said that anytime you have any brand,
and more, they was a whole day.
They need, they need, they need, they need to completely guard it to, uh,
uh, to access your pieces to it. So, we have a brand-day, uh, we did last two years.
You're five weeks of attendance.
It's just, it's just a real answer.
Um, I'm taking five weeks and everything falls away.
We're really, really helping to have an open day and this summer, which might be safer.
When that is, you really can't give you a concrete pay until we get those guys on side in a different way.
So, you know, whether it's, except with June, the first week in July,
we really want this public open this season.
Or even if it's a short time, you can get it open and see that project.
They don't, you know, when they get it?
They have material on side.
They're just waiting on, to die for the puricles.
We can do the notice to proceed.
And then they can start.
The whole, the, the whirling them up on is, we had the length for the size of the puricle to do the concrete repair.
That would be a little slower because we have to kept that net or out, and then put it back.
So, I don't know if we can get a section of it down and they come in and start.
They kind of mark in and hand.
That's just some logistics we have to lay out once we get their puricles not.
And we'll be having you come back to you with an update once we know more as the project's coming together.
And for my understanding that, things like that, that's out there for my area.
Actually, you know, a corner or a place of money.
I want you to go right on it.
I'll make a question to you.
I'll say that.
Heart first.
All right.
We'll start.
I'll work it.
I'll start.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Great team.
Exactly.
We're going to have to connect.
We're going to connect to the monogregoration.
We're going to connect to the leaders.
I have a board here.
Please.
the group 66 shared a stretch of it.
Well, we'll just show all of that to Portland, so I'll put it right in.
And you guys have an inner packet to the VA that you've had
have all the background information.
This is a little bit of history.
So the mayor's systems cooperative,
bison boards been meeting those six other months.
We usually meet monthly ones at conversations
from that board that's been community-privileged,
very in our community and how we go about to do some things
to try to get that back.
So the idea from that board was having a signature
survey by a left-end, and doing the research on it,
a lot of big estimations for these half of the time
playing over 66, and not really a big one at the moment.
Anyway, it's letting us run.
It's a much smaller scale, so we started looking at this,
and just trying to figure out how to incorporate that.
That type of idea here in my house.
So what we're looking at, from that board, from the C-B-D team,
under the community, I did, that's kind of the girl in our body,
was a two-day event during the research, which
no room-day was 65th event that happens anywhere
from Chicago to California.
During the time we would be looking at the last two-day
angelized, it would be a variety of side events,
looking at any bringing in a huge stage,
we would have Friday night bands, we would have side events,
a lot of different activities through the day on side of day.
At the last two-day research board, we had the rhetoric
of being represented on moving their big 5K and 10K event at the little run
to this thing, we gained as well.
A sheet is part of that group, and stuff from that board, too.
And we're looking at a five-day partial of that weekend,
in addition to a really counting-wide group of events,
something that a couple of months to do here,
and there's a girl with a shirt, a successful part committee,
a lot of people on the town just throughout the particular events,
and we're looking at the chartering out back to be a part of this.
So from that board, it didn't want to be tourism at the first board.
A few weeks ago, the special was held there,
just, you know, I'll just look at how we can do it,
and that brilliant, the special was held as well.
So then tonight, it's going to be you guys.
It's not something that made a budget in this fiscal year.
It's a new concept.
It's a new idea, so it's really on-around floor,
but I do feel like, I mean, it's just a run corner working for now.
The idea is that we will kind of take it eight times a book
from the city of Iraq, if you guys are familiar with that community,
it's outside of the Midwest City.
So we had an office called PAN, probably.
I really, listen, I don't know if I'm looking there below.
And just as an insight from then, we were connected to them,
and they found a key for a concept.
He went, they thought it was like, for then, with this.
I didn't think of that video initially.
So it was one day that they did city-of-air produced the event.
They had about 10,000 people in their park.
City-of-air has a city-of-bring budget.
It's 4 million dollars in here.
That's it.
They did this because they also did this by themselves
tax throughout the weekend and were very, very pleased.
So people was going to say, you need to get what
here, and then you see what they did.
So they got that out a letter from the city and in this office.
So basically, everything in the cities,
economic system, but they had been about business
but we were able to, this was actually
Joe and my compass.
And there are two reasons to go about all the business
that together that the city has spent $10,000 more
than we were with over the last two years.
And we've got about 130,000, the vendors,
and the workers' parents have had a sponsorship
with the last one from our business office.
And we will see, try to see donations to be able
to finance this event.
So, and around about, we're here tonight,
to have this session, to talk about it,
get some of it for you guys, and I'm a little bit
able to add anything else about it.
You've got a really well, I think, sort of,
wherever you know, sort of details about it.
Basically, the conversation is again,
a little bit like I said, we have a there.
It's an extremely successful event.
They were going to recover a lot of their experiences
by a group of self-tax.
I think we're going to have a very similar situation here.
This is a group of years, for the first of set out of the list,
we went through a lot of self-tax at the week scene.
This is a very small investment in our community,
that I think we'll have a significant difference.
Actually, very exciting, and I'm already a lot of great
high communities already, and I think people
excited that they have a community,
and some of the, this summer, we're going to get that
to some schools.
I'll second it.
Dr. Dumpel?
You're like four kids, or a partner?
Hi.
Thank you.
I'm 19.
They are going to register.
Got a bond.
I'm running.
I'm just off the signal.
Right, so I drew this short-s描.
So that last time I met Dr. Dumpel,
and we was hoping that it was going to be here this month,
and start, we kind of got that connection
to bring it over.
They want to come back in, and just pass off thoughts,
and imagine, and then it puts our first course
on the top of it, and we're not really thrilled
with that option.
So...
And there's some type of response, we all signed it, we sent it back to Gringo, we need to go today, and right now we're going on that's a worldwide access.
And basically, instead of doing a pain in the neck, which is allowed through a dot spec, we'd like to partition the loop asshole.
Read the fact, and start over.
Or at least talk about doing a different type of asphalt mix that the bridge that are over 70 saw spots.
I don't want to say it's kind of out of spot, and then 14 months, it moves and we've got follow in those links here.
So you're suggesting the impact.
So the state of suggestion right now is we could pick up all of the asphalt that they laid in December, that it's not needing connection.
And replace it, where we go with a 45 reinforcement for the last surface force over it on the spots that are emerging.
So we have some areas that are 91% infection, 92 is optimal.
And those are fine, but because they didn't be 92, normally you would be a payment option on folks.
So, but we would rather see some kind of 45 weeks over the top of that, or we would pick it back up.
Now, you have some areas that are less than an 8% in that state.
So there is no need to get it on those, and we'll put it in the asphalt back down to the spot.
How much should they lay in December?
And this is really just the stuff that they put down in November, and you see where they're going to shoot it.
The stuff that they lay in there is, for like 30 minutes from August to August, and then a little bit of second.
Yeah.
The second idea, there's a couple of spots that they were talking about.
There's one line between second and third we're talking about.
And then the stuff that's really an issue is third attitude.
So, that half of the block, it may need to take place in the third or third or third of their number of rivers.
The best of issues there.
And then there by a pinch off, there's some stuff that's not going to be easy.
And then basically half of the third street question thing.
We've got some local entities.
So right now we're going to go to respond back to us on the get-through.
We're going to accept our recommendations or if we're going to do something kind of fortifying asphalt mix over the top.
It's over the top of the bottom.
I don't know how you know else those up here, but we, we are beautiful.
You know, we do this right.
So I'll also look at that.
And I'm not sure what that would be a conflict is, but we want you to go on a good thing.
You want that.
You're all going to hear.
You're telling us what we need.
And we might be able to do that.
because we need to strike the first time, but not be working on all the time.
And that's, yeah, so we're working with Anderson right now because they have test results
and working with them on their condition based on test results and what's fixed as on abnormal.
So that's what we're talking about being there.
We're also, frankly, we need this done.
Very quickly.
Yeah.
And they still have to change their schedule.
They're still talking to her, they do.
And even if this will still be that.
Yeah.
Let's do all.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, I will have a tough time.
Going to guess what we're going to do again.
If they're a very successful,
the media is going to run away tomorrow or ready.
They have to contact or react to you.
They're asshole.
But you know, if you can use their asshole.
We can do that on this side.
It's similar.
So I'm going to have tough time with those guys.
But it didn't all live in here because we got businesses that are upset
because the streets are blocked off.
That says enough to that.
And I'm kind of disappointed that I've heard you.
Yeah.
So, soon we hear something going well.
Thank you.
Sorry.
The 20 players' relations that we're going here
and that you used to do a lot of other work.
And wait.
Okay.
But you said no.
The third try is mine.
All the things.
Thank you.
And we haven't had part of what you've had.
Did you know?
Was it after you got that?
Did you just thought that you were going to work?
No.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, there's a relationship with what parents have used to do.
One of those library, four parents, five or so or two people.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Okay.
I'll make the notes.
Thank you.
This is the reason why I'm talking about it.
Okay.
You know what you said?
Let me do that.
I do.
That's what it was.
That's why I'm talking about our dance,
and the community of announcements.
And I would like to talk about how you are using your jeep into the talk a little bit.
But our first argument is, as I said, God, over the last month, not the, you know,
the experience of the last month.
That will, for the entire time, it's very close.
But of course, the technological impact, the struggle from this perspective.
And so, they don't get the, yeah, it was that the shit gets,
it's not what they've talked a little bit about what all they're doing.
And I think we appreciate it.
I think we have to make it a brand-new stop.
They have done this in a crowd of jobs.
And it's not just mind-blowing as far as the biggest tool we have right now is the partnership with all of our communities.
Now we have the research we work very well with them.
And we have a great partnership there, and I just couldn't get by.
And that, with the assistance of the tribe, we used to have the prototype right now.
It works well together.
And because of that, great things are happening.
We need to have the work where you've gone to you.
So, we'll come to events.
Exactly what we can have.
Great.
There's some kind of issues in the community.
We'll say these kind of events.
And we're taking a jump on that.
We'll have, of course.
They usually have our here at an RPD.
And it's just been a huge force, both by force.
And it cooperates.
And we really track that that in these sort of dangerous areas.
It kind of helps to appreciate anything.
And, of course, that's all we're going to do.
There's a lot of their cars involved.
It's fun to talk about them.
Another, I agree.
Our cars were asked.
They said that by the time of the map.
And I'll shoot by you.
A little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a way.
And 45 times of cash there.
And another way.
But one of them.
Just continue to work with the assets.
Continue to work with the series.
And as you know, we've, we've, we've, we've,
have got to the東京 grounds with the,
another 10 wilden dealt with accounts,
and we're coming across a dam.
We need, uh, we've always smoked three days later on boards.
Continuously, same page, but we've just done an incredible job of tracking them.
Before we continue to, to make.
And this is our last time we were here today.
We going to work with it all day in our day.
This doesn't make really good.
and this is something great now, and I don't know if they're all the very long
course we absolutely do this is a great partnership and we're fortunate that
you've worked like that and I've been able to do that and this is a great job.
Thank you very much for letting me know if you'd like me to brag on for a minute.
And the other thing we're talking about is I don't know about apology and a big thing you can work.
So you said that there is a part of the Department or spirit part of everyone to pick up and see why I came back to the team.
My channel is work community and I just wanted to.
There was a scratch problem everywhere.
And I know that I don't produce a burden on you guys.
That wasn't really my camp.
I don't know how long you guys, but the happened to you guys.
I didn't know that well.
I appreciate that.
But the total cost of being there were 534.3 tons of trash.
So over many of them, I have the trash and all that I can do.
But it ain't going to be expensive as well.
And they're not our outside contractors.
They're so much.
But I knew to appreciate all of your all your staff and the crews went out and did that.
There were some like 600 buyers too.
600 buyers.
We're taking that out of the unit.
So I know around all of that after you can see it.
I mean, you can see that we've talked a little bit about that.
They've got a great difference.
So again, I appreciate you.
It's fast.
And they've all of that sort of overloaded this week.
But they have some of those very much needed in our community.
Which is a way of addition to the five hundred and three more tons.
And then we have trash and we have additional 19.4.
And then we also have those two becomes.
And I think last year, when we meet 500 pounds of trash here.
So we actually bring you some much I want to have to wait.
So it's all set.
It's the exact.
It's all about.
It's good to see you just not here.
I don't know if you have a second name on that.
All right.
I'm going to come forward.
Sit down.
Appreciate it.
All right.
I'm going to have much to have tonight.
We're going to talk about street rules, arts and events.
We have a great cleanup.
And it kind of runs out of all of the highlights in the last few weeks.
Whether you're having a good set.
Have any questions?
Did you get some of the names?
Jerry.
I think we still don't know.
We didn't hear you.
Tyler and I have to do.
Well, there is just like last week.
And they are still trying to get five members of what their costs will be.
And I believe that Tyler is trying to get from wrong.
They're still hoping they might be some call back.
So that's still their costs might be not able to do it.
Or we have to be.
That's not the character.
So if you think they're going to get to their cost, then we'll go.
and we'll go online to the American government and the customers.
So the trustworthy is this that we get asked at the time and actually
encourage people who are here to trust and hope that we hear something from them
from time to time, time to have the idea as part of the anticipation of the debate.
There's a year-to-date meeting tomorrow, and I was going to do it to the end.
And they're going to hopefully do a little bit more of a certain increase in the
media and the power of the judgment.
People didn't really came to me at all, but I have to get some more information tomorrow.
We've talked a little bit about that.
We also had that area in the local church.
We also had technical reading with people who were hurt, and they had spoken all the
council members, you know, they can.
We can definitely say that.
I think most of the time everyone probably did receive kind of a tool up there.
Something on that.
But that kind of briefing.
I don't know how it was to stick to the event.
The property could be licensed.
We could make a little bit of a presence around the presence there.
But I'm going to imagine that there will be some great information in the local community.
Okay.